// Quiz questions

var questZombi  = [
    {
    question: "Where do most of the Resident Evil games takes place?",
    choices: {1: "Raccon City", 2: "Chernobyl", 3: "Midgar"},
    correctAnswer: 1
},  {
    question: "What is Nemesis' signature saying?",
    choices: {1: "Die", 2: "Excelsior!", 3: "S.T.A.R.S...."},
    correctAnswer: 3
}, {
    question: "What is the name of the company of released the virus that caused the pandemic?",
    choices: {1: "Umbrella", 2: "WeylandUtani", 3: "OCP"},
    correctAnswer: 1
},{
    question: "What is the name of virus that causes the global pandemic?",
    choices: {1: "COVID-19", 2: "T-Virus", 3: "Blacklight Virus"},
    correctAnswer: 2
},{
    question: "What item is used in the original series to save your game?",
    choices: {1: "Ink Ribbon", 2: "Game Cartridge", 3: "Camera"},
    correctAnswer: 1
},{
    question: "What weapon is used to usually kill a boss in one hit?",
    choices: {1: "Magnum", 2: "Rocket Launcher", 3: "Knife"},
    correctAnswer: 2
},{
    question: "Resident Evil is a series based on____.",
    choices: {1: "Demons", 2: "Serial Killers", 3: "Zombies"},
    correctAnswer: 3
},{
    question: "_____is the name of a devloper behind Resident Evil.",
    choices: {1: "Konami", 2: "Capcom", 3: "Square Enix"},
    correctAnswer: 2
},{
    question: "In Resident Evil 3, Jill Valentine was constantly stalked and attacked by which B.O.W?",
    choices: {1: "Mr.X", 2: "Nemesis", 3: "Thanos"},
    correctAnswer: 1
},{
    question: "In Resident Evil 4, which handgun is available from the merchant for free after destroying 10-15 Blue Medallions?",
    choices: {1: "Punisher", 2: "Blacktail", 3: "Red Nine"},
    correctAnswer: 1
},{
    question: "In the live-action movie what is the name of the Supercomputer built to protect company assesrs",
    choices: {1: "GlaDOS", 2: "Red Queen", 3: "HAL 9000"},
    correctAnswer: 2
},{
    question: "Which Resident Evil game was the first one to be played from a first-person perspective?",
    choices: {1: "Resident Evil 7:biohazrd", 2: "Resident Evil:Code Veronica",3: "Resident Evil:Umbrella Chronicles"},
    correctAnswer: 1
},{
    question:"____is the name of the shades wearing, cold deameaner, murderous Umbrella company executive protagonist",
    choices: {1: "Elle Woods", 2: "Agent Smith", 3: "Albert Wesker"},
    correctAnswer: 3
},{
    question:"While the series is called Resident Evil in the west, in the east it's called _____",
    choices: {1: "Infestation", 2: "Dead Resistance", 3: "Biohazard"},
    correctAnswer: 3
},{
    question:"____ is the name of the scientist who developed the T-Virus",
    choices:{1: "Dr. James Marcus", 2: "Dr. Charles Ashford", 3: "Dr. Neil deGrasse Tyson"},
    correctAnswer: 2
}
];
